Mahin Khandker

(347) 433-9849 | mahinkhandker706@gmail.com | Queens, New York https://www.linkedin.com/in/mahin-khandker-883938186/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Meticulous problem solver with 460+ training hours and experience developing full-stack Java applications. Dedicated to acquiring a career that will allow me the prospect to excel in software development as well as highlight my previous work experience and leadership abilities.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

W3Schools JavaScript Certification (in progress; expected date of completion 06/2021)

- Java
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Spring Boot

- Spring Data JPA
- Spring Security (JWT)
- Bootstrap
- REST API's
- SQL

- Unit Testing (JUnit, Mockito)
- SOLID OOP Principles
- Dependencies Injection
- Gir

EXPERIENCE

Generation Junior Full Stack Java Developer Program | Feb 2023- July 2023

Training Participant

- Participating in a 16-week, 460+ hour Junior Full Stack Java Developer program that emphasizes hands-on practical application
- Learning and deploying the technologies involved in creating full-stack web applications with Java using Spring Boot Framework, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3
- Implementing basic unit tests and deploying the application to Heroku

Target | Elmont, NY | November 2022 - January 2023

Tech Consultant

- Accommodated guests need in the tech and electronics section with exceptional service and upheld brands standards to ensure satisfaction
- Diligently checked the newest sales and deals to stay up to date with the newest offerings
- Performed data entry using POS systems to keep track of inventory stock

The Home Depot | Elmont, NY | May 2021 - April 2022

Receiving Associate

- Assisted in unloading and stocking merchandise while checking the quality of the products
- Entered information about incoming merchandise into the store's computer system
- Advised customer needs and delivered adequate service to ensure customer satisfaction

EDUCATION

Stony Brook University of the State University of New York

Bachelor of Science, Technological Systems Management

August 2022 - Present

City College of the City University of New York

Bachelor of Science, Undeclared

August 2021 - May 2022